Guide to the Office of the President Records, Alan Simpson Files, 1949-1979
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Office of the President Records, Alan Simpson Files
1949-1979
Vassar College. Office of the President, Simpson, Alan, 1912-1998
Simpson, Alan, 1912-1998
91 cubic feet (94 boxes)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
Materials related to the work of the Vassar College's Office of the President during the tenure of Alan Simpson. The collection includes typical day-to-day administrative records, as well as documents related to noteworthy issues and events from the Simpson Era (1964-1977).
Biographical Note
Alan Simpson was the seventh President of Vassar College. He was British-born and educated. He grew up in Newcastle-on-Tyne, and studied history at both Oxford University and Harvard University. His tenure as president (1964-1977) coincided with a volatile period in U.S. history, with particular difficulties centered on U.S. campuses. Simpson was also president when the college made the decision to admit men.
Scope and Content Note
Correspondence, memoranda, clippings, articles, speeches, and press releases related to the work of Vassar College's Office of the President during the tenure of Alan Simpson. The collection includes typical day-to-day administrative records, as well as documents related to issues and events of note from the Simpson Era (1964-1977). Topics covered include: the curriculum, coeducation, men's education and the Vassar-Yale Study; the Black Studies Program, the Women's Studies Program, and other interdisciplinary programs; campus response to the Civil Rights Movement, the Vietnam War, and the second wave of the Women's Rights Movement; and construction of the Terrace Apartments, All Campus Dining Center (ACDC), Powerhouse Theater, and the Lockwood addition to Thompson Library.
Access
Some files in this collection are restricted and labeled as such in the container list. Other material may need to be vetted before being released. The rest is open for research according to the
regulations of the Vassar College Archives and Special Collections Library
without any additional restrictions.
Related Materials
Additional materials related to Alan Simpson's presidency can be found in the following Vassar College archival collections:
1969 Black Studies Student Sit-In
Clyde Griffen Coeducation and Men's Education Collection
Vassar College Biographical Files
Vassar College Photograph Files
Subject Headings
Organizations:
Vassar College--Presidents; Vassar College--Administration; Vassar College--Public relations; Vassar College--Students
Subjects:
African Americans--Study and teaching; Black people--Study and teaching; Coeducation; College students--Political activity; Women--Education; Women, Black--Education; Women's studies
Document Types:
Correspondence; Financial records; Minutes (administrative records); Printed ephemera; Reports; Scrapbooks; Speeches (documents)
VCL Categories:
Vassar College Presidents
Encoding Information
Encoded by Zachary Bodnar and Laura Streett, December 2014.
Updated by Mark Seidl, December 2019.
Updated by Emma Gronbeck, July 2024.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Vassar College Office of the President, 2002.
Series List
- Series I. Trustees and Administration, 1960-1978; (Boxes 1-17)
- Series II. Buildings and Grounds, 1960-1974; (Box 18)
- Series III. Faculty, 1955-1978; (Boxes 19-33)
- Series IV. Alumnae/i, 1949-1979; (Boxes 33-37)
- Series V. Within the College, 1951-1979; (Boxes 38-64)
- Series VI. Associations, 1958-1977; (Boxes 65-73)
- Series VII. Without the College, 1962-1976; (Boxes 73-74)
- Series VIII. Colleges and Universities, 1961-1977; (Boxes 74-76)
- Series IX. Special Projects and Events, 1956-1975; (Boxes 76-87)
- Series X. Personal, circa 1955-1977; (Boxes 87-89)
- Series XI. Additions, circa 1958-1979; (Boxes 89-94)
Container List
- Series I. Trustees and Administration, 1960-1978
  - President’s Report to the Trustees, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.1)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.2)
  - Budget Committee, 1964-1966 (Folder 1.3)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.4)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mr. Wilkie, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.5)
  - Committee to Reconsider Central Dining, 1960-1966 (Folder 1.6)
  - Food Services (Ellis Committee), 1964 (Folder 1.7)
  - Development Committee, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.8)
  - Food Service Proposals, 1964 (Folder 1.9)
  - Inauguration, 1964 (Folder 1.10)
  - Inauguration Committee, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.11)
  - Investments & Finance Committee, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.12)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.13)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.14)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.15)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1963-1965 (Folder 1.16)
  - Faculty V Studies, 1964 (Folder 1.17)
  - Faculty and Study Committee Reports, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.18)
  - Comptroller — General, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.19)
  - Comptroller — Fringe Benefits, 1964 (Folder 1.20)
  - Comptroller’s Report to Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1965-1966 (Folder 1.21)
  - Treasurer’s Reports, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.22)
  - General Manager, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.23)
  - General Manager’s Reports, 1964-1965 (Folder 1.24)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mr. Wilkie, 1965-1966 (Folder 1.25)
  - President’s Report to the Trustees, 1965-1966 (Folder 1.26)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mr. Wilkie, 1966-1967 (Folder 1.27)
  - Trustees — B, 1965-1967 (Folder 1.28)
  - Trustees — C, 1965-1967 (Folder 1.29)
  - Trustees — D, 1965-1967 (Folder 1.30)
  - Trustees — E, 1965-1967 (Folder 1.31)
  - Trustees — F, 1965-1967 (Folder 1.32)
  - Trustees — H, 1965-1966 (Folder 1.33)
  - Trustees — L, 1966-1967 (Folder 1.34)
  - Trustees — M, 1966 (Folder 1.35)
  - Trustees — P, 1966-1967 (Folder 1.36)
  - Trustees — R, 1965-1967 (Folder 1.37)
  - Trustees — S, 1965-1967 (Folder 1.38)
  - Trustees — V, 1966-1967 (Folder 1.39)
  - Trustees — W, 1965 (Folder 1.40)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1966-1967 (Folder 2.1)
  - By-Laws of the Board of Trustees, 1966 (Folder 2.2)
  - Trustee By-Laws (old), 1965 (Folder 2.3)
  - Legal Counsel, 1964-1966 (Folder 2.4)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1965-1966 (Folder 2.5)
  - Budget Committee, 1965-1968 (Folder 2.6)
  - Budget Committee Minutes, 1965-1967 (Folder 2.7)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1965-1966 (Folder 2.8)
  - Development Committee, 1965-1967 (Folder 2.9)
  - Dormitory Planning Committee, 1965-1966 (Folder 2.10)
  - Committee to Consider Central Dining, 1966 (Folder 2.11)
  - Investment and Finance Committee, 1965-1966 (Folder 2.12)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1966-1967 (Folder 2.13)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1965-1967 (Folder 2.14)
  - Undergraduate Life Committee, 1965-1967 (Folder 2.15)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1965-1966 (Folder 2.16)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1966-1967 (Folder 2.17)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Folder 2.18)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1965-1966 (Folder 2.19)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1966-1967 (Folder 2.20)
  - Faculty V Studies — Working Papers, 1965-1966 (Folder 2.21)
  - Faculty V Studies — Budget, 1966-1967 (Folder 2.22)
  - Vice President for Administration, 1965 (Folder 2.23)
  - Vice President for Administration (Mr. Ritterskamp), 1966-1967 (Folder 2.24)
  - Comptroller — General, 1965-1967 (Folder 2.25)
  - Comptroller — General, 1966-1967 (Folder 2.26)
  - Comptroller’s Reports to Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1965-1966 (Folder 2.27)
  - Comptroller’s Reports to the Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1966-1967 (Folder 2.28)
  - Comptroller — National Defense Student Loan Fund, 1967 (Folder 2.29)
  - Budget, 1965-1967 (Folder 2.30)
  - Comptroller — Fringe Benefits, 1965 (Folder 2.31)
  - Treasurer’s Reports, 1965-1966 (Folder 2.32)
  - Treasurer’s Reports, 1966-1967 (Folder 2.33)
  - General Manager, 1965-1966 (Folder 3.1)
  - Review of Pension Benefits for Vassar College, 1966 Mar (Folder 3.2)
  - General Manager, 1966-1967 (Folder 3.3)
  - General Manager’s Reports, 1965-1966 (Folder 3.4)
  - Union Negotiations and Contract, 1966 (Folder 3.5)
  - Department of Halls, 1966 (Folder 3.6)
  - Personnel Office, 1965-1966 (Folder 3.7)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mr. Wilkie, 1967-1968 (Folder 3.8)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mr. Wilkie, 1968-1969 (Folder 3.9)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mrs. Purcell, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.10)
  - Trustees — B, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.11)
  - Trustees — B, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.12)
  - Trustees — C, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.13)
  - Trustees — C, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.14)
  - Trustees — D, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.15)
  - Trustees — D, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.16)
  - Trustees — E, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.17)
  - Trustees — E, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.18)
  - Trustees — F, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.19)
  - Trustees — F, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.20)
  - Trustees — G, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.21)
  - Trustees — G, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.22)
  - Trustees — H, 1967-1968 (Folder 3.23)
  - Trustees — J, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.24)
  - Trustees — J, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.25)
  - Trustees — L, 1967-1968 (Folder 3.26)
  - Trustees — L, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.27)
  - Trustees — M, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.28)
  - Trustees — M, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.29)
  - Trustees — P, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.30)
  - Trustees — R, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.31)
  - Trustees — R, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.32)
  - Trustees — S, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.33)
  - Trustees — S, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.34)
  - Trustees — V, 1967-1969 (Folder 3.35)
  - Trustees — V, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.36)
  - Trustees — W, 1967-1968; (empty) (Folder 3.37)
  - Trustees — W, 1969 (Folder 3.38)
  - Regents Conference for Trustees, 1968-1970 (Folder 3.39)
  - President’s Report to the Trustees, 1967-1968 (Folder 3.40)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1967-1968 (Folder 3.41)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1968-1969 (Folder 3.42)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.43)
  - Vassar Board of Trustees — Informal Meetings, 1967 (Folder 3.44)
  - President’s Report to the Trustees, 1969-1970 (Folder 3.45)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1969 (Folder 3.46)
  - Board of Trustees — General Material Circulated for meeting, 1969 Oct 18 (Folder 3.47)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1969 (Folder 3.48)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (Black Studies Material), 1970 (Folder 3.49)
  - Board of Trustees — Report of Actions Taken at Meeting, 1970 May (Folder 3.50)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1968-1969 (Folder 3.51)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1969-1970 (Folder 4.1)
  - Budget Committee, 1967-1969 (Folder 4.2)
  - Budget Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 4.3)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1967-1969 (Folder 4.4)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1968-1969 (Folder 4.5)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 4.6)
  - Capital Campaign Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 4.7)
  - Development Committee, 1967-1968 (Folder 4.8)
  - Development Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 4.9)
  - Forward Planning Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 4.10)
  - Forward Planning Committee, 1968 (Folder 4.11)
  - Forward Planning Committee, 1968-1969 (Folder 4.12)
  - Investment and Finance Committee, 1967-1969 (Folder 4.13)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1968-1969 (Folder 4.14)
  - Investment and Finance Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 4.15)
  - Investments and Finance Committee — Proxies and Corporate Responsibility (IBM and Vietnam War), 1970 (Folder 4.16)
  - Joint Committee on Minority Students, 1970 (Folder 4.17)
  - Trustee Advisory Committee on Minority Students, 1970 (Folder 4.18)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1967-1969 (Folder 5.1)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.2)
  - Trustee Organization Committee, 1969 (Folder 5.3)
  - Trustee Organization Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.4)
  - Trustee Committee on Poughkeepsie Day School, 1970 (Folder 5.5)
  - Undergraduate Life Committee, 1967-1969 (Folder 5.6)
  - Undergraduate Life Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.7)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1967-1968 (Folder 5.8)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1968-1969 (Folder 5.9)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.10)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1969 Nov (Folder 5.11)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1970 Mar (Folder 5.12)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Folder 5.13)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Folder 5.14)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.15)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1967-1968 (Folder 5.16)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1968-1969 (Folder 5.17)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.18)
  - Vice-President for Administration — J. Ritterskamp, 1967-1969 (Folder 5.19)
  - Vice-President for Administration, 1968-1969 (Folder 5.20)
  - Vice-President for Administration, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.21)
  - Vice-President for Administration — Reports to Trustees, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.22)
  - Union Negotiations and Contract, 1967-1968 (Folder 5.23)
  - Union Negotiations and Contract, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.24)
  - Comptroller — General, 1967-1968 (Folder 5.25)
  - Comptroller, 1968-1969 (Folder 5.26)
  - Comptroller, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.27)
  - Comptroller’s Reports to Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1967-1968 (Folder 5.28)
  - Comptroller’s Reports to Executive Committee and Board of Trustees, 1968-1969 (Folder 5.29)
  - Comptroller’s Reports to Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.30)
  - Comptroller — National Defense Student Loan Fund, 1967-1969 (Folder 5.31)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Folder 5.32)
  - Budget, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.33)
  - Treasurer’s Reports, 1967-1968 (Folder 5.34)
  - Treasurer’s Reports, 1968-1969 (Folder 5.35)
  - Treasurer’s Reports, 1969-1970 (Folder 5.36)
  - General Manager, 1967-1968 (Folder 5.37)
  - General Manager’s Reports, 1967-1968 (Folder 5.38)
  - Department of Halls, 1967-1968; (empty) (Folder 5.39)
  - Director of Plant Operations, 1967-1969 (Folder 5.40)
  - Personnel Office, 1967-1968 (Folder 5.41)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mrs. Purcell, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.1)
  - Trustees — B, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.2)
  - Trustees — C, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.3)
  - Trustees — E, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.4)
  - Trustees — F, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.5)
  - Trustees — G, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.6)
  - Trustees — J, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.7)
  - Trustees — L, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.8)
  - Trustees — M, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.9)
  - Trustees — O, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.10)
  - Trustees — P, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.11)
  - Trustees — R, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.12)
  - Trustees — S, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.13)
  - Trustees — V, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.14)
  - Trustees — W, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.15)
  - Regents Conference for Trustees, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.16)
  - Board of Trustees — Report of Actions Taken at Meetings, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.17)
  - President’s Reports to the Trustees, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.18)
  - Legal Counsel (Carroll Wainwright), 1970-1971 (Folder 6.19)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.20)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.21)
  - Budget Committee, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.22)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.23)
  - Capital Campaign Committee, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.24)
  - Development Committee, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.25)
  - Forward Planning Committee, 1970-1971; (empty) (Folder 6.26)
  - Investments and Finance — Proxies and Corporate Responsibility, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.27)
  - Investment and Finance Committee, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.28)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.29)
  - Trustee Organization Committee, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.30)
  - Trustee Committee on Poughkeepsie Day School, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.31)
  - Undergraduate Life Committee, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.32)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.33)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1970 Sep (Folder 6.34)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1970 Nov (Folder 6.35)
  - Executive Committee Meeting (Including Student Conference), 1971 Mar (Folder 6.36)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1971 Apr (Folder 6.37)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.38)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.39)
  - Vice-President for Administration, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.40)
  - Director of Special Projects, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.41)
  - Vice-President for Student Affairs — Reports to Trustees, 1970-1972 (Folder 6.42)
  - Vice-President for Administration — Reports to Trustees, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.43)
  - Union Negotiations and Contracts, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.44)
  - Comptroller, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.45)
  - Budget, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.46)
  - National Defense Student Loan Program, 1970 (Folder 6.47)
  - Director of Plant Operations, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.48)
  - Personnel Office, 1970-1971 (Folder 6.49)
  - Ad Hoc Joint Committee on the Education of Minority Students, 1970 (Folder 6.50)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mrs. Purcell, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.1)
  - Trustees — B, 1971-1973 (Folder 7.2)
  - Trustees — C, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.3)
  - Trustees — E, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.4)
  - Trustees — F, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.5)
  - Trustees — G, 1971-1976 (Folder 7.6)
  - Trustees — J, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.7)
  - Trustees — M, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.8)
  - Trustees — O, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.9)
  - Trustees — P, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.10)
  - Trustees — R, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.11)
  - Trustees — S, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.12)
  - Trustees — V, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.13)
  - Trustees — W, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.14)
  - President’s Report to the Trustees, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.15)
  - Annual Regents Conference on Leadership Role of Trustees, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.16)
  - Legal Counsel (Carroll Wainwright), 1971-1972 (Folder 7.17)
  - Board of Trustees Report of Proceedings, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.18)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.19)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.20)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes (with attachments), 1972 May (Folder 7.21)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1971 Sep (Folder 7.22)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1971 Dec (Folder 7.23)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1972 Feb (Folder 7.24)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1972 May (Folder 7.25)
  - Budget Committee, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.26)
  - Committee on Allocations, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.27)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.28)
  - Capital Campaign Committee, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.29)
  - Development Committee, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.30)
  - Forward Planning Committee, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.31)
  - Trustee Committee on Governance, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.32)
  - Trustee Ad Hoc Committee on the Graduate Center, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.33)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.34)
  - Investments and Finance Committee — Reports, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.35)
  - Investments and Finance Committee Proxies and Corporate Responsibility, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.36)
  - Joint Committee on Minority Students, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.37)
  - Committee on Minority Students, 1972 (Folder 7.38)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.39)
  - Undergraduate Life Committee, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.40)
  - Committee on Women at Vassar (Women Studies Program), 1971-1972 (Folder 7.41)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.42)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1971 Nov (Folder 7.43)
  - Executive Committee Conference (Trustee/Faculty), 1971 Dec (Folder 7.44)
  - Meeting of Executive Committee and Forward Planning Committee, 1972 Mar (Folder 7.45)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 May (Folder 7.46)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Folder 7.47)
  - Faculty and Studies (President Simpson’s file), 1971-1972 (Folder 8.1)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1971 Nov (Folder 8.2)
  - Faculty and Studies Meeting, 1972 Jan (Folder 8.3)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1971-1972 (Folder 8.4)
  - Vice-President for Administration, 1971-1972 (Folder 8.5)
  - Vice-President for Administration — Reports to Trustees, 1971-1972 (Folder 8.6)
  - Vice-President for Student Affairs — Reports to Trustees, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.7)
  - Director of Special Projects, 1971-1972 (Folder 8.8)
  - Budget Planning, 1969-1970 (Folder 8.9)
  - Financial Problems, 1967-1971 (Folder 8.10)
  - Budget, 1971-1972 (Folder 8.11)
  - Comptroller, 1971-1972 (Folder 8.12)
  - Director of Plant Operations, 1971-1972 (Folder 8.13)
  - Personnel Office, 1971-1972 (Folder 8.14)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mrs. Purcell, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.15)
  - Trustees — B, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.16)
  - Trustees — C, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.17)
  - Trustees — D, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.18)
  - Trustees — E, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.19)
  - Trustees — G, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.20)
  - Trustees — M, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.21)
  - Trustees — O, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.22)
  - Trustees — P, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.23)
  - Trustees — R, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.24)
  - Trustees — S, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.25)
  - Trustees — V, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.26)
  - Trustees — W, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.27)
  - Legal Counsel (Carroll Wainwright), 1972-1973 (Folder 8.28)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1972 (Folder 8.29)
  - Board of Trustees — General, 1973 (Folder 8.30)
  - President’s Report to the Trustees, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.31)
  - Board of Trustees — Report of Proceedings, 1972-1973 (Folder 8.32)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1972 Oct (Folder 8.33)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1972 Dec (Folder 8.34)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1973 Feb (Folder 8.35)
  - Board of Trustee Meeting, 1973 May (Folder 8.36)
  - Trustee Meeting Minutes (and Attachments), 1972 Dec (Folder 8.37)
  - Trustee Meeting Minutes (and Attachments), 1972 Oct (Folder 8.38)
  - Board of Trustees Minutes and Attachments, 1973 Feb (Folder 8.39)
  - Trustee Minutes and Attachments, 1973 May (Folder 8.40)
  - Report of the President — Draft, 1971-1972 (Folder 8.41)
  - Report of the President — Draft, 1971-1972 (Folder 9.1)
  - Report of the President — Draft and Notes, 1971-1972 (Folder 9.2)
  - Allocations Committee: Sub-Committee of Budget Committee, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.3)
  - Budget Committee, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.4)
  - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.5)
  - Capital Campaign Committee, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.6)
  - Trustee Committee on Conference, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.7)
  - Development Committee, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.8)
  - Development Committee Meeting, 1973 Jan (Folder 9.9)
  - Forward Planning Committee, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.10)
  - Governance, 1973 (Folder 9.11)
  - Investments and Finance Committee — Proxies and Corporate Responsibility, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.12)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.13)
  - Joint Committee on Minority Students, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.14)
  - Committee on Nominations, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.15)
  - Committee on Women: Trustees Seminar on the Role of the Sexes in a Changing Society, 1972 (Folder 9.16)
  - Committee on Women, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.17)
  - Report of the Committee on Women, 1972 May (Folder 9.18)
  - Committee on Women at Vassar (Responses to Report), 1972-1973 (Folder 9.19)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.20)
  - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.21)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 Sep (Folder 9.22)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1973 Mar (Folder 9.23)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1973 Apr (Folder 9.24)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.25)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee Meeting, 1972 Nov (Folder 9.26)
  - Vice-President for Administration, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.27)
  - Vice-President for Administration — Reports to Trustees, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.28)
  - Union Negotiations and Contract, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.29)
  - Director of Special Projects, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.30)
  - Comptroller, 1972-1973 (Folder 9.31)
  - Board of Trustees Agenda, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.32)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mrs. Purcell, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.33)
  - Trustees — B, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.34)
  - Trustees — C, 1973-1974 (Folder 9.35)